let questions = [{
        numb: 1,
        question: "Which function do we use to shuffle a list(say list1)?",
        answer: "random.shuffle(list1)",
        options: [
            "random.shuffleList(list1)",
            "random.shuffle(list1)",
            "A and B",
            "None of these"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 2,
        question: "st=”Cadbury Dairy Milk” x=st.split(‘a’) print(len(x)) What is the output of the above code?",
        answer: "3",
        options: [
            "9",
            "3",
            "6",
            "7"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 3,
        question: "print(ord(‘abc’)) What is the output of the above code?",
        answer: "sorted(tuple)",
        options: [
            "sorted(tuple)",
            "tuple.sorted()",
            "sort(tuple)",
            "tuple.sort()"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 4,
        question: "Which of the following is used to create an empty set?",
        answer: "set()",
        options: [
            "{}",
            "set()",
            "[]",
            "{}"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 5,
        question: "Which one of the following has the highest precedence in the expression?",
        answer: "Parentheses",
        options: [
            "Addition",
            "Multiplication",
            "Exponential",
            "Parentheses"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "What is the maximum length of a Python identifier?",
        answer: "No fixed length",
        options: [
            "32",
            "16",
            "128",
            "No fixed length"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "Which of the following is used to define a block of code in Python language?",
        answer: "Indentation",
        options: [
            "Indentation",
            "Key",
            "Brackets",
            "All of the mentioned"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "Which of the following functions can help us to find the version of python that we are currently working on?",
        answer: "sys.version(1)",
        options: [
            "sys.version(1)",
            "sys.version(0)",
            "sys.version()",
            "sys.version"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "Which of the following is true for variable names in Python?",
        answer: "unlimited length",
        options: [
            "underscore and ampersand are the only two special characters allowed",
            "unlimited length",
            "all private members must have leading and trailing underscores",
            "none of the mentioned"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "Which of the following is the use of id() function in python?",
        answer: "Id returns the identity of the object",
        options: [
            "Every object doesn’t have a unique id",
            "Id returns the identity of the object",
            "All of the mentioned",
            "None of the mentioned"
        ]
    },



];